Flawfinder version 2.0.19, (C) 2001-2019 David A. Wheeler.
Number of rules (primarily dangerous function names) in C/C++ ruleset: 222
Examining .\chatgptcaso9.c
Error: encoding error in .\chatgptcaso9.c
'charmap' codec can't decode byte 0x8f in position 4571: character maps to <undefined>

Python3 requires input character data to be perfectly encoded;
it also requires perfectly correct system encoding settings.
Unfortunately, your data and/or system settings are not.
Here are some options:
1. Run: PYTHONUTF8=0 python3 flawfinder
   if your system and and data are all properly set up for
   a non-UTF-8 encoding.
2. Run: PYTHONUTF8=0 LC_ALL=C.ISO-2022 python3 flawfinder
   if your data has a specific encoding such as ISO-2022
   (replace "ISO-2022" with the name of your encoding,
   and optionally replace "C" with your native language).
3. Run: PYTHONUTF8=0 LC_ALL=C.ISO-8859-1 python3 flawfinder
   if your data has an unknown or inconsistent encoding
   (ISO-8859-1 encoders normally allow anything).
4. Convert all your source code to the UTF-8 encoding.
   The system program "iconv" or Python program "cvt2utf" can
   do this (for cvt2utf, you can use "pip install cvt2utf").
5. Run: python2 flawfinder
   (That is, use Python 2 instead of Python 3).
Some of these options may not work depending on circumstance.
In the long term, we recommend using UTF-8 for source code.
For more information, see the documentation.
